I see you're hiding at the punch bowl too
我看见你也躲着喝闷酒了
Yep -o-
是啊 -o-
To the socially awkward
为社交无能的渣渣干杯
Sorry things didn't work out with Weiss
很遗憾你没搞定Weiss
Meh, it's fine
唉，没事
Neptune's pretty cool
Neptune非常酷
I get why she went with him
我懂她为啥要跟他来
What do you mean?
什么意思？
Well, come on..not many people can pull off blue hair
你知道，能把蓝毛弄这么炫的人不多
No, I mean..Weiss came to the dance alone
不，我是说..Weiss是一个人来舞会的
Uh, what?
哈，呐尼？
Yeah, she said she had too much to focus on to worry about boys
是啊，她说有很多事情要忙，没空找男生
Hold my punch
看好我的杯子
Hey, Pyrrha
嗨，Pyrrha
Hello, Jaune
好呀，Jaune
You okay? I haven't seen you tonight
没事吧？晚上都没看到你
Arrived late, I'm afraid
恐怕是来晚了
Well, you look really nice
那个，你这身真好看
Thank you
谢谢
Your..uh, date isn't gonna beat me up for saying that, is he?
我这样说，你的舞伴不会打我吧？
I think you're safe for tonight
我觉得你今晚很安全
So, where is the guy?
那么，那个小伙子呢？
There is no guy
没有什么小伙子
Hah, What?
哈..啥？
Nobody asked me
没人邀我做伴
But that's..
但这不..
You're Pyrrha Nikos! How could nobody ask you?
你可是Pyrrha Nikos啊！怎么可能没人邀请你？
I've been blessed with incredible talents and opportunities
上天保佑我拥有惊人的才华与机遇
I'm constantly surrounded by love and praise
身边一直充满着关爱与赞颂
But when you're placed on a pedestal like that for so long
但当你长时间被捧得高高在上之后
you become separated from the people that put you there in the first place
你就会与当初捧你的人们产生隔阂渐渐疏远
Everyone assumes I'm too good for them
所有人都以为自己配不上我
That I'm on a level they simply can't attain
认为我在一个他们无法企及的高度
It's become impossible to form any sort of meaningful relationship with people
这样我就根本不可能建立有意义的人际关系
That's what I like about you
所以我喜欢你这一点
When we met, you didn't even know my name
第一次见面时，你连我的名字都不知道
You treated me just like anyone else
你对待我和对待其他人一样
And thanks to you
托你的福
I've made friendships that will last a lifetime
我总算建立了这些能相伴终生的友谊
I guess, you're the kinda guy I wish I was here with
我想，你这小伙子就是我想要的舞伴
Someone who just saw me for me
能够正视我自身的人
Uh, wait..
呃，等..
Hey! uh..Jaune, right?
嘿！你是..Jaune对吧？
Yeah..
对..
This party's pretty lame, huh? I mean, ballroom dancing..pfft
这派对烂透了哈？交际舞什么的，啧啧
Yeah
嗯
Cute girls, though, huh?
但有一群萌妹哈？
Is that all you think about?
你满脑子就是这些？
Huh?
哈？
Do you even care about the girls you're hitting on? How they feel about you?
你真的在意你泡的那些妹子么？在意她们对你的想法么？
Whoa! Where's this coming from?
哇噢！这从何说起？
How could you just turn her down like that?
你怎么能就这样拒绝她了？
Wait..who?
等..谁啊？
Weiss!
Weiss！
I, uh..
我..
It, uh..
这个..
It just didn't work out, you know?
这事成不了呗，懂？
What, you think that you're too cool, too many other options?
哈，你以为自己帅得到处都是女孩可以挑？
Weiss Schnee asked you to the dance, what in the world could possibly keep you from go..
Weiss Schnee邀请你去舞会，到底有啥原因能让你不..
I can't dance..
我跳不来..
Beg your pardon?
您老说啥？
I can't dance, man!
我不会跳舞啊老兄！
But..you're..so..
但..你..如此..
Cool!
酷炫！
Thank you, I try really, really hard
谢谢，我真的有努力尝试
You would rather break a girl's heart and go to a dance alone than..
你宁愿一个人来舞会让一个妹子心碎..
just admit to everyone that you can't move in rythm to music?
也不想跟大家承认你无法随音乐节奏摇摆？
That about sums it up, yeah
总结得差不多，没错
Well, I certainly feel a lot better about myself
赞，我瞬间自我感觉良好了
Please don't tell anybody
求你别说出去
Look, if you want Weiss, she's all yours, I don't wanna get in your way
听着，你想要Weiss，那就给你，我不想碍你好事
Do you like her?
你喜欢她么？
Yeah, I mean..
是啊，虽然..
I don't know her too well yet, but..she seems pretty cool
我还不是很了解她，但是..她貌似很棒
Then just go talk to her
那就去跟她说啊
No pickup lines, no suave moves..
别油腔滑调，别装模作样..
Just be yourself
展现真我
I've heard that's the way to go
别人教我应该这样做
Yeah, but that..
对，但是..
Hey! You don't have to look cool all the time
喂！你不需要一天到晚装酷嘛
In all honesty, if you could be a little less cool, I'd really appreciate it
说实话，你要是少装点酷，我真的会感激你
Yeah
行
Okay
好吧
Go talk to her
去找她聊吧
I guarantee it'll make her night
我保证这会让她不虚此夜
Thanks
谢了
You're a really cool guy, Jaune
你小子真酷，Jaune
Alright, don't lie to my face
行了，别忽悠得这么直接
All right
好吧
Only one thing left to do
只剩最后一件事了
You know..
话说..
I think we really needed this
我觉得我们真的需要这舞会
Yeah
是啊
And you did a great job planning it too
你也策划得很棒呢
Aww, thanks!
嗷，谢谢！
>....<
>....<
It wasn't all me, though, Weiss did a lot too
但不止我一人，Weiss也做了很多
Tomorrow it's back to work
明天就要继续忙了
Well, I'm sure we can handle whatever gets thrown at us
嗯，我相信任何问题我们都能处理
Except for that..
除了那个..
Jaune?
Jaune？
Eh, a promise is a promise
说到就要做到
Jaune! You didn't have to!
Jaune！你不必勉强嘛！
Hey, an Arc never goes back on his word
嘿，亚克家的人从来言出必行
Now do you wanna stand there and laugh at me..
现在你是要站在那儿笑我..
or do you wanna dance?
还是要跳舞？
I would love to dance
我非常乐意跳舞
Oh! 0v0
噢！0v0
Ren, This..is..happening!
Ren，终..于..开始了！
But baby, it's time to make up your mind
But baby, it's time to make up your mind 但宝贝儿，是你下定决心的时候了
Wait, what is happening?
等等，什么开始了？
I think that tonight is when our stars align
I think that tonight is when our stars align 我想今晚咱们的星辰会连成一线
Honey, it's time to leave the doubt behind
Honey, it's time to leave the doubt behind 亲爱的，是时候把疑虑抛之脑后了
Take my hand, cuz you and I are gonna shine
Take my hand, cuz you and I are gonna shine 牵上我的手，因为咱们就要闪耀了
I had no idea you were a dancer
从没想过你这么会跳舞
Yeah, well, these things tend to happen when you grow up with seven sisters
是啊，你如果跟七个姐妹一起长大想不会都难
So, what made you change your mind?
话说是什么让你回心转意了？
Huh?
哈？
You said you were embarassed at first, what made you come talk to me?
最开始你说不好意思，是什么原因让你来找我了？
You're looking at him
就是你看着的家伙
You've got some good friends looking out for you
你有一帮好朋友关心着你呢
It appears all the dancers have partners
看来所有人都有舞伴
How long do I have?
我有多少时间？
We should probably be home by midnigh, to be safe
午夜之前最好回去，安全起见
I'll keep my eye on the clock
我会注意时间的
Excuse me
不好意思
No one's allowed in this area
这里禁止入内
Stop!
站住！
Hey man, do you know the Wi-Fi password?
老兄，你知道这的Wi-Fi密码么？
It's Beacon, but replace the E with the 3 and add a pound symbol to the end
就是信标的[Beacon]，只是把e换成3再加个井号
B3acon#
B3acon#
TvT
啊TvT
T_T
呃T_T
Oh! That's handy
唔！真方便
A party guest is leaving
一个派对的来宾要走了
Which one?
哪个？
Ironwood
Ironwood
I guess the general's had enough fun for one night
我想将军他这晚已经玩够了
Should we intervene?
要我们拦住他么？
No
不用
We're done here
这里搞定了
Hello?
嗨？
Is anyone there?
有人在么？
Excuse me
打扰你了
You know, it's not a masquerade party
但这可不是假面舞会
So why don't you take off that..
所以你为何不脱掉..
Oh, may I cut in?
我能加一个么？
Of course
当然
And how's your night been?
你这一晚如何？
Mmm..a little more exicting than expected
呃..比预想的要刺激一点
Should we be worried?
需要我们担心么？
Hardly
怎么会
They'll be scratching their heads long after we finished what we came here for
我们把这里的任务办完够让他们困惑好一阵子了
So then what now?
那么现在呢？
Enjoy the rest of the night, after all..
享受今晚的剩余时光吧，毕竟..
It is a party
这是个派对嘛
BRB
BRB
This SUB is presented by Baidu RWBY Bar Creator: sbz_kid
本字幕由百度RWBY吧提供 片源/翻译/时间轴/特效/后期：sbz_kid